<main>
<newgame>Start game</newgame>
<credits>Credits</credits>
<yes>Yes</yes>
<no>No</no>
<q1>Archbishop wishes to enter the country dry law.[The people's discontent can be dangerous.]</q1>
<q2>the Witch saw fit to cancel the fine for swearing on the streets.</q2>
<q3>According to the Archbishop, now the youth are becoming immoral! He wants to introduce a Law of God for study in schools.</q3>
<q4>the Witch asks to raise the price of services of drug treatment.</q4>
<q5>To educate, the Archbishop requires the introduction of a chaplain in the army ranks.</q5>
<q6>In the words of the Archbishop, to study in military schools should only baptized people.</q6>
<q7>General requires higher wages to army.</q7>
<q8>Diplomat writes a complaint against the Prime Minister - he is constantly in conflict with the ambassadors of other States. Should we change the Minister?</q8>
<q9>West asks for help in the war with the East. General openly 'For'. Will Help The West?</q9>
<q10>the East and South are planning to attack us! Whether to ask the North for help?</q10>
<q11>General thinks to introduce compulsory military service for women. You will allow him?</q11>
<q12>King of the West came to visit! Take it?</q12>
<q13>Incomes fall, sire. We need to reform. Hold?</q13>
<q14>what if we bring the army to a contract basis? This will help saddamite people!</q14>
<q15>the Church wishes to impose a tax on rites! Afford?</q15>
<q16>the Prince wants to zabotit 'a feast for the whole world.' Do you approve?</q16>
<q17>to Raise the retirement age seems economically beneficial?</q17>
<q18>Elise bothered me! Maybe we should have a new favourite?</q18>
<q19>whether to build the hospital? In order to protect from epidemics!</q19>
<q20>Miners want a raise, otherwise they will not go down into the mines.</q20>
<q21>Witch need supplies for experiments. Will you help?</q21>
<q22>Your wife wants more power! What do you say?</q22>
<q23>We, as a civilized society, it is time to legalize euthanasia! Although for a considerable fee.</q23>
<q24>Found the body of a merchant! To conduct an investigation?</q24>
<q25>trouble, as long as the boys study together with the girls!</q25>
<q26>to Prepare for the Spring festival? This year it will be great!</q26>
<q27>Sire, your sweat contains a high dose of rhododendrons. Suggest to abandon today's tournament!</q27>
<q28>Queen of the South gave us the gift of books! To Build The Library?</q28>
<q29>Psychology is a pseudoscience! Do you agree?</q29>
</main>